Little Heroes is a family, tv movie film directed by Craig Clyde.
Tomboy and farmgirl Charlene "Charley" Wilson finds fun and adventure with her beloved dog Fuzz and tries to
fit in to her small town, while her parents struggle with money and crop production worries.
Charley Wilson, played by Raeanin Simpson.
Mrs. Evans, played by Reta Patterson.
Alonzo, played by Keith Christensen.
Virgil Wilson, played by Craig Clyde.
Fritz, played by Lance Johnson.
Rachel Wilson, played by Katherine Willis.
Little Man Tate is a 1991 American drama film directed by Jodie Foster (in her
directorial debut) from a screenplay written by Scott Frank.
The film stars Adam Hann-Byrd as Fred Tate, a seven-year-old child prodigy who struggles to self-actualize
in social and psychological settings that largely fail to accommodate his intelligence.
It also stars Foster,  Dianne Wiest,  Harry Connick Jr.,
David Hyde Pierce, Debi Mazar and P.J.
Little Man Tate was released theatrically on October 18, 1991, by
Orion Pictures to critical and commercial success.
Reviewers praised Foster's direction, Frank's
screenplay and the  performances of the cast.
The film grossed $25 million domestically, on a  $10 million budget.
The tone is lighthearted.